https://transmagic.com/privacy-policy

Effective date: November 3, 2014
TransMagic, Inc. (“TransMagic,” “we,” “us,” and “our”) owns and operates this website (this “Site”). This Online Privacy Policy (this “Policy”) describes our commitment to privacy and reflects the importance we place on earning and keeping your trust.
Contents
Scope of This Policy
This Policy applies only to information that TransMagic collects about or related to you through this Site. It does not apply to information that TransMagic collects through other channels, such as through telephone, in-person communications, other websites, or its software products.
Some of the information TransMagic collects through this Site may be “personal information”—information that identifies you personally, alone or in combination with other information available to us. Other information may be nonpersonally identifiable, such as your IP address.
TransMagic has provided this Policy so that you will know what information TransMagic collects, how TransMagic uses this information, the types of third parties with whom TransMagic may share this information, and some of the choices that are available to you.
This Policy may be supplemented or amended from time to time by additional privacy notices (“Privacy Notices”), provided at the time we collect your information. For example, certain pages of this Site may contain Privacy Notices providing more details about the information we collect on those particular pages, why we need that information, and choices you may have about the ways we use that information. In other cases, specific Privacy Notices may be required to comply with the privacy laws of one of the countries, provinces, or states in which we do business.
Your Consent
By using this Site, you are consenting to the collection, use, disclosure, and transfer of your information as described in this Policy (and any Privacy Notices that apply to you). If you do not consent to the collection, use, disclosure and transfer of your information as described in this Policy (and any Privacy Notices that apply to you), you may not use this Site. If you have questions about this Policy, or any Privacy Notice, please contact us via e-mail at info@transmagic.com.
Our Terms of Use
This Policy is part of the Terms of Use that govern your use of this Site. A link to our Terms of Use is provided at the bottom of each page of this Site.
Your Choices
In General. We respect your right to make choices about the ways we collect, use, and disclose your information. This Policy describes some of your choices, such as your choice to opt out of receiving “cookies.” We may ask you to indicate your choices at the time and on the page where you provide your information.
Email preferences. You can opt out of promotional emails we send to you. If you wish to stop receiving promotional emails, simply select “unsubscribe” located at the bottom of each communication.
Do Not Track Mechanisms. California law requires this Policy to address how we respond to any “Do-Not-Track (‘DNT’) signal” delivered by your browser. Because of the changing state of technology and indecision within the industry regarding the meaning of DNT signals, we currently do not make any guarantee that we will honor DNT signals.
Previously Expressed Preferences. You may be able to change previously expressed preferences regarding how we use your information. Please email us at info@transmagic.com if you want to change your preferences.
This Policy May Change
TransMagic reserves the right to update or modify this Policy and any Privacy Notice, at any time and without prior notice, by posting the revised version of the Policy or Privacy Notice on this Site. These changes will only apply to the information we collect after we have posted the revised Policy or Privacy Notice on this Site.
Your use of this Site following any such change constitutes your agreement that all information collected from or about you after the revised Policy is posted will be subject to the terms of the revised Policy. You may access the current version of this Policy at any time by clicking on the link marked “Privacy” at the bottom of each page of the public areas of this Site.
Information We Collect
Information You Manually Provide. TransMagic collects the information you manually provide (using your keyboard, mouse, or touchpad) when you use this Site. For example, we collect the information you provide when you request information about our products and services, sign up for our email newsletters, participate in a live chat, or otherwise communicate with us or interact with this Site. Some of the information you manually provide may be personal information, such as your name and contact information.
Information from your browser or device. TransMagic collects information that is sent to us automatically by your web browser or mobile device. This information typically includes your IP address, the name of your operating system, the name and version of your browser, the date and time of your visit, and the pages you visit. The information we receive may depend on your browser or device settings.
The information we receive from your web browser and device is not, in and of itself, personally identifiable. Generally, we use this information in the aggregate to help us improve this Site and make it more compatible with the technology used by our visitors. However, we may combine it with other information in an attempt to identify you or we may combine it with information that does identify you. We may also review our server logs for security purposes—for example, to detect intrusions into our network—and we might share our server logs, which contain visitors’ IP addresses, with the appropriate investigative authorities who could use that information to trace and identify you.
Information Collected by Cookies and Other Technologies. We use “cookies” and other technologies to collect information and support certain features of this Site. For example, we may use these technologies to:
collect information about the ways visitors use this Site—which pages they visit, which links they use, and how long they stay on each page;
support the features and functionality of this Site—for example, to save you the trouble of reentering information already in our database or to prompt the settings you established on previous visits;
personalize your experience when you use this Site; and
improve our marketing efforts, including through use of targeted advertising.
The information we collect using cookies and similar technologies is not, in and of itself, personally identifiable, but we may link it to personal information that you provide. If you do not wish to receive cookies, you may set your browser to reject cookies or to alert you when a cookie is placed on your computer. Although you are not required to accept cookies when you visit this Site, you may be unable to use all of the functionality of this Site if your browser rejects our cookies.
Information About Third-Party Cookies
In addition to the cookies TransMagic delivers to your computer or mobile device through this Site, certain third parties may deliver cookies to you for a variety of reasons. For example, we use Google Analytics, a web analytics tool that helps us understand how visitors engage with our Sites. To learn more about Google Analytics, click here.
Other third parties may deliver cookies to your computer or mobile device for the purpose of tracking your online behaviors over time and across nonaffiliated websites and/or delivering targeted advertisements either on this Site or on other websites.
You have choices about the collection of information by third parties on our Sites. For example, if you don’t want information about your visit to this Site sent to Google Analytics, you may download an Opt-out Browser Add-on by clicking here. Please note that the Add-on does not prevent information from being sent to TransMagic.
In addition, if you would like to opt-out of having interest-based information collected by certain entities during your visits to this Site or other websites, please click here. You will be directed to an industry-developed website that contains mechanisms for choosing whether each listed entity may collect and use data for online behavioral advertising purposes. It may be that some of the third parties that collect interest-based information on this Site do not participate in the industry-developed opt-out website, in which case the best way to avoid third-party tracking of your online behaviors may be through your browser settings and deletion of cookies.
How We Use Your Information
Generally, we use the information we collect through this Site:
to provide the information, products and services you request;
to provide you with effective customer service;
to provide you with a personalized experience when you use this Site;
to contact you with information and notices related to your use of this Site;
to contact you with special offers and other information we believe will be of interest to you (in accordance with any privacy preferences you have expressed to us);
to invite you to participate in surveys and provide Feedback to us (in accordance with any privacy preferences you have expressed to us);
to improve the content, functionality and usability of this Site;
to better understand your needs and interests;
to improve our products and services;
to improve our marketing and promotional efforts;
for security, credit or fraud prevention purposes; and
for any other purpose identified in an applicable Privacy Notice, click-through agreement or other agreement between you and us.
How We Share Your Information
With Third–Party Vendors. TransMagic may share information collected through this Site with third-party vendors who act for us or on our behalf. For example, we may use third-party vendors to design and operate this Site; to conduct surveys; and to help us with our promotional efforts. These third-party vendors may need information about you to perform their functions.
With Our Third-Party Resellers. TransMagic may share information collected through this Site with our third-party resellers. For example, if you contact us to inquire about our products or services, we may share your contact information with our reseller who operates in your geographic area so that the reseller can contact you directly and answer your questions.
With Other Users of this Site. You may be able to submit User-Generated Content on or through this Site. In this Policy, “User-Generated Content” or “UGC” refers to content that you post using the social networking tools we make available to you and that does not constitute “Feedback” (as that term is defined in our Terms of Use). Any personal information contained in UGC can be read, collected, or used by others. In addition, we may use UGC you submit for advertising campaigns and other promotions. We may or may not use your name in connection with such use, and we may or may not seek your consent before using the content for such purposes. Therefore, you should have no expectation of privacy with respect to UGC you submit on or through this Site.
With Third-Party Social Media Platforms. We may provide functionality on this Site that allows you to automatically post information about the actions you take on this Site to a third-party social media platform (such as Facebook or Twitter). If you choose to take advantage of this functionality, people with access to your profile on the third-party platform may be able to see the actions you have taken. Thus, you should have no expectation of privacy in those actions. Further, if you choose to link your profile on this Site with an account on a third-party social media platform, we may share the information in your profile with that third-party platform.
With Other, Carefully Selected Business Partners. From time to time, we may share your information with selected third parties for their own marketing purposes. For example, we may partner with third parties to sponsor contests or other promotions, and we may share with these third parties the information you submit to us to participate in the contest or take advantage of the promotion. Before doing so, however, we may offer you the opportunity to “opt out” or “opt in,” as required by applicable law.
In Aggregate or De-Identified Form. We use information collected through this Site to create a compiled, aggregate view of usage patterns. We may share aggregate information with third parties so they can better understand our user base. We may also share with third parties information about how particular individuals use this Site, but only on a de-identified basis (“Individualized Data”). Individualized Data is not personally identifiable, but it does reflect the usage patterns of a particular Site user, as opposed to Site users collectively.
As Part of a Business Transfer. Your information may be transferred to successor organization if, for example, we transfer the ownership or operation of this Site to another organization or if we merge with another organization. If such a transfer occurs, the successor organization’s use of your information will still be subject to this Policy and the privacy preferences you have expressed to us.
To Comply with Laws and Protect Our Rights and the Rights of Others. We may disclose your information when we, in good faith, believe disclosure is appropriate to comply with the law, a court order or a subpoena. We may also disclose your information to prevent or investigate a possible crime, such as fraud or identity theft; to protect the security of this Site; to enforce or apply our online Terms of Use or other agreements; or to protect our own rights or property or the rights, property or safety of our users or others.
As Described in a Privacy Notice or click-through agreement. We reserve the right to disclose your information as described in any Privacy Notice posted on a page of this Site where you provide that information. By providing your information on that page you will be consenting to the disclosure of your information as described in that privacy notice. We also reserve the right to disclose your information as described in any click–through agreement to which you have agreed.
How We Protect Your Information
TransMagic takes reasonable precautions to provide a level of security appropriate to the sensitivity of the information we collect. Although we use reasonable measures to help protect your information against unauthorized use or disclosure, we cannot guarantee the security of information provided over the Internet or stored in our databases and will not be responsible for breaches of security beyond our reasonable control.
Children’s Privacy
You must be at least 16 years old to have our permission to use this Site. We do not knowingly collect personal information from visitors under 16 years of age. If you are under the age of 16, please do not use this Site.
Links to Other Websites
This Policy applies only to this Site. If you visit another Transmagic website, please take a moment to review the privacy policy posted on that site to learn what information may be collected through that site and how it is processed.
This Site may also contain links to websites that are not operated by TransMagic. These links are provided for your reference and convenience only and do not imply any endorsement of the products sold or information provided through these websites, nor any association with their operators. TransMagic does not control these websites and is not responsible for their data practices. Any information you provide to third parties on their websites is covered under their privacy and data collection policies and is not covered by this Policy. We urge you to review the privacy policy posted on any site you visit before using the site or providing any personal information.
Access to Your Information
If you would like to review, correct and update the personal information you have provided to us through this Site, please contact us by email at info@transmagic.com. We will respond to your request within the time limit set out by the applicable privacy legislation. We will use reasonable efforts to comply with your request as required by applicable law.
Retention of Personal Information
TransMagic retains the personal information collected on this Site as long as necessary to provide the services, products and information you request or as permitted by applicable law.
This Site Is Hosted on Servers Located in the United States.
TransMagic is a U.S. corporation. The servers that support this Site are located in the United States. While it is in our possession, your information will generally be stored in TransMagic databases or databases maintained by our third-party service providers on servers and data storage devices located in the United States. U.S. data protection laws may not provide as much protection as the data protection laws in force in some other countries, however, we will process your information in accordance with this Policy no matter where our data is stored. If you are located in a country outside the United States, by using this Site you consent to the transfer of your information to the United States.
Governing Law
This Policy shall be governed under the laws of the State of Colorado United States of America without regard to its conflicts of law provisions.
Questions About This Policy or TransMagic’s Data Practices
If you have questions or concerns about this Policy, any Privacy Notice, or TransMagic’s data practices, please contact us by email at info@transmagic.com. You may also contact us at:
TransMagic, Inc.
11859 Pecos St., Suite 310
Westminster, CO 80234
Tel: +1 303 460 1406
